hello everyone welcome back to my
channel ICA Lombard and Karnataka Bank
join forces for insurance tie
up so Karnataka bank has partnered with
ICICI Lombard General Insurance Company
Limited to offer enhanced Insurance
Solutions and customer benefits to its
patterns a media statement said the
offerings through this tieup include
health insurance Moto Insurance travel
insurance home insurance catering to the
diverse insurance needs of individuals
and businesses alike quoting shakar ra
executive director of Karnataka Bank the
statement said our collaboration with IC
Lombard underscores this commitment and
reinforces our efforts to offer Best
inclass Insurance
Solutions further bank is EMB working on
digital Insurance initiatives which will
empower the bank's customers to
conveniently access and manage their
insurance policies through digital
platforms this includes online policy
purchase realtime claims processing and
personalized Insurance advisory Services
ensuring a hasslefree
experience Ananda singi chief retail and
government ICC Lombard said partnering
with Karnataka Bank celebrated for its
unwavering dedication to Excellence
presents a compelling opportunity to
broaden our horizont and present
customers with a holistic Insurance
portfolio so thank you for listening
thank you for watching thank you
everyone bye